<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="storyContents">
        <item>
            One day the buffalo was bathing in the river, when he had finished working,
            he bathed all day until the sun covered it. The next day the buffalo was walking
            somewhere but there was an animal that was getting cold because of the extreme cold
            and needed his help and it was a goat. Not only in the cold weather but also the wind,
            rain and darkening of the sky also increased.\n\n When the buffalo saw the goat that
            it was cold, he went to the place to help but the goat was very afraid of the water
            because he could get wet. What the buffalo did was haul some banana leaves and make
            it like a hut so that the goat could have a shelter.\n\n The next day, they realized that
            the weather was fine when they got out of the hut made by the buffalo. The goat was
            very grateful to the buffalo because he didn\'t get wet and the buffalo even took care
            of it. In time they became friends wherever they met. The goat continues to put in his
            sincere heart what the buffalo did to help him.\n\n
            Helping is caring!\n\n
        </item>
        <item>
            A Hare was making fun of the Tortoise one day for being so slow.\n\n
            "Do you ever get anywhere?" he asked with a mocking laugh.\n\n
            "Yes," replied the Tortoise, "and I get there sooner than you think. I\'ll run you a race and prove it."\n\n
            The Hare was much amused at the idea of running a race with the Tortoise, but for the fun of the thing he agreed. So the Fox, who had consented to act as judge, marked the distance and started the runners off.\n\n
            The Hare was soon far out of sight, and to make the Tortoise feel very deeply how ridiculous it was for him to try a race with a Hare, he lay down beside the course to take a nap until the Tortoise should catch up.\n\n
            The Tortoise meanwhile kept going slowly but steadily, and, after a time, passed the place where the Hare was sleeping. But the Hare slept on very peacefully; and when at last he did wake up, the Tortoise was near the goal. The Hare now ran his swiftest, but he could not overtake the Tortoise in time.\n\n
            The race is not always to the swift.\n\n
        </item>
        <item>
            One bright day in late autumn a family of Ants were bustling about in the warm sunshine, drying out the grain they had stored up during the summer, when a starving Grasshopper, his fiddle under his arm, came up and humbly begged for a bite to eat.\n\n
            "What!" cried the Ants in surprise, "haven\'t you stored anything away for the winter? What in the world were you doing all last summer?"\n\n
            "I didn\'t have time to store up any food," whined the Grasshopper; "I was so busy making music that before I knew it the summer was gone."\n\n
            The Ants shrugged their shoulders in disgust\n\n
            "Making music, were you?" they cried. "Very well; now dance!" And they turned their backs on the Grasshopper and went on with their work.\n\n
            There\'s a time for work and a time for play.\n\n
        </item>
        <item>
            The Mice once called a meeting to decide on a plan to free themselves of their enemy, the Cat. At least they wished to find some way of knowing when she was coming, so they might have time to run away. Indeed, something had to be done, for they lived in such constant fear of her claws that they hardly dared stir from their dens by night or day.\n\n
            Many plans were discussed, but none of them was thought good enough. At last a very young Mouse got up and said:\n\n
            "I have a plan that seems very simple, but I know it will be successful.\n\n All we have to do is to hang a bell about the Cat\'s neck. When we hear the bell ringing we will know immediately that our enemy is coming."\n\n
            All the Mice were much surprised that they had not thought of such a plan before. But in the midst of the rejoicing over their good fortune, an old Mouse arose and said:\n\n
            "I will say that the plan of the young Mouse is very good. But let me ask one question: Who will bell the Cat?"\n\n
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>